Translated by Releska
The sky is shining
It's a day like this
I'll go to the hospital
To the hospital
I'll take the dream of a boy
Of course, you and I always
I don't even know what to say
It's time for the light to shine
There's always a smile on your lips
You and you
If you love me,
I'll be able to meet you in person
I don't feel like I can do anything
A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A, who is it?
No-no-no-no-no.
After I actually decided on a drive- Feeling proud of myself,
We finally got our job and became an embodiment of our new world.
I wonder where it started and I wonder if it would return to the old world.
But I never thought so.
It seemed to be the same as the family of Kyo-ryu-san,
and it was fun to have fun together with other people together!
From Yu-fou to Oji-sama!
Is this the place where Kami-na-ryu is located?
Is it the place where Kami-na-ryu is located?
Yes, of course!
Good!
This way!
Switch 4!
This is the place where Kyo-ryu-san is located!
Let's think about the real world!
What?
In order to do that, we should make the same situation the same way!
If Kami-na-ryu uses that power,
he will be able to change the power of the other people!
That's right!
It's good that it's good, but...
What?
Komo is lying!
It's true!
All right, let's go!
Yay!
What's going on here?
If Kyo-ryu doesn't want to come here again today,
what's going on here?
What?
What's going on here?
I'll leave it to you!
Oh, I heard it!
It's 5 o'clock!
It's coming back!
Hey!
Is this Kami-na-ryu?
Please come back when it's hot!
It's hot!
That's why I said it's getting better!
What's that?
Huh?
Wow?
I'm sure it's coming!
Shimota!
Kami-na-ryu is trying to make a mistake
and make a mistake!
What?
A mistake?
It's 5 o'clock now!
Are you all right now?
I can't believe it's coming back!
It's getting hot!
It's a little hot!
What's going on here?
Let's see the evil Dragon King!
The Ivory Seidokishi, Pandore Gaia!
You are here to defeat us!
The mysterious Gen of the 5-day old man.
I won't let you go, 5-day old man.
You can't do it!
You're not going to die!
I'll make you feel better.
Rizugi!
What about me?
I'll help you!
If you're scared, you're the only one who can do it!
Yaaaaaaaaaaah!
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Yaaaaaaaaah!
What is it?
I want to be a man!
Hime!
What are you doing, Brother?!
It's all my feelings.
Please forgive me, my precious Kazugazu.
It was just a heavy blow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye bye.
Be careful.
It's still raining.
It's okay.
It's always raining.
But...
Don't you want to go?
Look, it's not for people to fight.
It's different from that.
There's a house in the house.
It's a small house.
If you don't have a dragon here,
you have to hurry up.
But...
The ship is in that state.
It's not a place to sell.
It's not a place to sell the ship.
If you say so,
it's a place to sell the ship.
It's a place to sell the ship.
I'm determined.
Me too.
Thank you, everyone.
I found it.
There it is.
I find it again.
I found it again.
I'm sorry.
Take it.
Make a move different.
Try it like this.
Okay.
I'm going to heighten this part.
I'm going to be looking around a little.
That one's cool.
You're right.
Huh?
Don't you have a drink?
Huh? Do you have a drink?
If you want to have a drink, you can do it!
Jumper!
Open the door!
What's this?
This is a drink!
Excuse me, Mr. Hazuki.
When you're home, please give me a hug.
You're giving me a hug?
That's because you're free.
When you're here, I can see your hands.
I've never seen such a thing like you.
You have courage and determination.
And you're beautiful.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm looking for Mr. Fiancé, the CEO of Grand Moon.
In the past two months, Hime has been the owner of Dragon Seijin.
I can't go home until I find Hime.
If you save Hime, you won't be able to see me anymore.
You have a long way to go.
It's a path that I can live with.
Let's do our best.
Yes.
Where are you going?
Don't you think you changed your mind?
I don't think so.
Excuse me.
It's an alias barbecue, so let's go to the kitchen.
I'm so excited to see you.
That's great.
I'm going to have a drink.
We all have to be friends.
We'll never see each other again.
That's true.
We'll be a couple of friends.
Don't try to fight.
We'll do whatever we can do.
I like that.
Andre is quite cool.
Oh, I see.
Is that so?
Good evening.
Good evening, I'm Marikyu.
Thank you very much.
Marikaga Morima!
Goethe number 5.
Who are you calling?
I heard that you were looking forward to seeing someone.
I'll call you to the address.
Goethe number 5.
Please come in.
Hi, Andory.
Is this?
It's a sea, but can you eat this with your hands?
It's interesting.
Can you eat it with your hands with your eyes?
Maybe you can eat it with your hands with your hands with your hands?
Yeah.
Well, what do you want?
Do you have a big hand?
Yeah.
I use the things that are in the big bag with the diamond ruby.
Wow!
Good job!
Maybe it's Andory's mother's big hand.
It's a bad joke.
It's amazing that you can hear it in the wind.
If you don't, I'll be in trouble.
Andres-sama, tonight we'll be in the middle of the night.
We'll be in the middle of the night.
Lankan-sama, what do we do?
I'll be in trouble.
Andres-sama, stop at home.
I'm okay.
No, everyone.
I'm grateful for your help.
I don't want to leave my wife.
If you're a captain, you're the one to blame.
It's hard to find Himesama.
Himesama, are you going to be in trouble?
No, I'm not.
I'm not going to be in trouble.
I'm sorry.
I'll be in trouble.
I'm not going to be in trouble.
So you're going to be in trouble?
That's right.
I believe Hime is beautiful like a rabbit.
Wait, wait.
Huh?
Yeah.
I love you.
What are you doing?
Shut up.
Oh, no.
I'm not going to be in trouble.
You know what?
You're doing things uselessly.
I want to hear it too.
I'm sorry.
I let you know that,
from the start.
I got to know you guys,
what you have to think,
what you have to think.
Ah, that's right. The color is different from the color of the secret.
I was told to be a man's head.
Shiteki! This is Mr. Andrew's one-on-one!
It looks like he's out of the TV game.
I'm sure he's going to really fly to the universe.
Shut up, Shizuka.
Do you know how much I've fly?
No, that's the most important thing to find.
This is the chip of the Emeralds who made this little thing.
Ah! I can't believe it!
That's why I can't find the Spear.
Tell me the truth!
Or the shape, or the shape.
If you all find it, you'll find it.
That's right. I'll find it.
Is that so? You'll find it again?
Then, let's do what you want to do.
It's time for me to find it.
That's right. I'll find it.
Is there anything else you want to do?
Actually, I've been thinking of a few things that I want you to do.
What kind of things?
It's a diamond that has a lot of things to do.
A diamond? And that big one?
I'll find it. I'll find it again!
Ah...
Is it true that it's a diamond or a Emerald?
I can't do that kind of thing.
What are you saying? It's for me!
I used an enormous amount of money.
I want to make a living! I want to make a living!
I want to make a living!
What's that?
It's so far away...
Ah, I don't like that kind of thing.
Let's go for a walk.
Wait for me, please wait.
What?
Please finish this off.
Wait for me.
I was really relieved.
I'm not dead.
This is the one to lead the Reddy.
Now, what about you?
You're the Reddy, aren't you?
You're not dead, are you?
I'm not.
You're not the only one who can make a fool of your nose.
You're a fool of your nose.
I don't need you.
I'll find you.
You're not the only one who can make a fool of your nose.
I've never seen you like that.
He is a asshole!
Give me a favor!
You try to hurt yourself like a prince.
But you are just a meritorious one.
So you suggest you take good care of yourself.
Not really, but just to let everyone fall in control of their hearts.
I want to ask you to meet the people you meet with me.
I will wait for you to meet you all the way back.
What?
Look, look.
Do you understand?
It's my bad luck.
This isn't food.
Where?
Did something happen?
Look.
Is that flower a gift?
Yeah.
It's not bad, but it's embarrassing to everyone.
Androgynous.
I feel like I'm using something in my chest.
Is it a disease?
Oh, that's it?
Look.
It's hard.
I have to do something in front of my chest.
But if I take that, Androgynous will be here.
I have to do that.
I'm thinking of something.
Androgynous has something important to do.
Hey!
Androgynous!
No!
I found something.
It's a diamond.
I did it!
It's a piece of cake.
Look.
Is this something?
Are you okay?
It's okay.
If you put that diamond on my chest, I'll kill you.
Please be careful.
It looks like it's a diamond.
Androgynous has to look for Emerald's chest.
It's not like that.
What's that?
Is it a stone?
It's a piece of cake.
Where is it?
Hey, why don't you just use your card card and find your creature or perfume laughed.
Okay?
I like something happens with different type.
I like a higher level of people, so that's why I considered you more at the same level.
Then I took the bigger packages and took the smallerтеque to make their dogs.
Why did I also get yours right?
Take it!
Do you think I understand that?
Wow.
I don't even know what to do.
You're so good at acting! You're so good at acting!
You're so good at acting!
Andru-san!
Satoi! This way!
You're so good at acting!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
What's wrong?
I can't see.
I'm sorry.
Now!
What's wrong?
We're all sorry.
...Sorry...
Get in my way, you!
It's so expensive!
It's 5th time, I couldn't find a chance to see you without me.
I don't have to worry about you, but I will make you feel better.
Or, I will keep your promise.
Thank you.
Oh, it's my first time to see you.
So cute!
Now we're going to do it!
Ok, let's go!
I'm not going to do a tail-trip!
What is that sound?!
I like it! I can do it!
Alright, let's go!
What's going on?!
I'm sorry!
Thank you very much.
It's a wonderful thing to see.
It might be a wonderful day.
I wonder if I can find Riff Hime.
If I can find her, then what should I do?
That's right. The two of us are the same.
If I don't have a chance, I want to come back to the shop.
I have to do my best to do that.
What?
It's just poison.
It's a waste of time.
Let's do our best.
Goodbye, my prince.
Pair, pay, pay, pay, pay, pay, pay, pay.
Paradise, come, come, come, come, come, come, come!
Whoever you are, even who you are,
Stay at my house.
I'm flying, flying, flying.
I always have a voice that I'm always in
I'm listening to this song
Those who are strange, who are these
The thing is that they're always the same
The difference is that the tone of the middle finger is a heart
Bay of Bay of Bay of Bay of Bay of Baht
It's a bit too动y F Boardiness
Misaky-Fugi Fugi Fugi Fugi Yoyo
Shownou Miyunagoi na Yokimime
Da no sigou sal過去
Allio
Satori wo ni de yo
Why did you eat the egg in the microwave?
I ate it in the microwave again, right?
Mugamu...
What?
You're kidding?
Are you okay?
You're probably fine.
You're a bit worried about the five-point failure.
Mugamu...
Huh?
No.
Well, then, maybe it's true!
Next time, Mugamu Kappara Daisu.
Mugamu Kappara Daisu.
See you again, Mugamu.